A Guide to the Charles Uht photographs FA103
Rockefeller Archive Center
Charles Uht photographs
undated
Rockefeller Archive Center
Uht, Charles
FA103
6 Cubic Feet 29 document boxes.
File Plan
Former Classification: P/1072
Scope and Contents
The Charles Uht Photograph Collection documents collections of art and belongings acquired by Nelson A. Rockefeller, Laurance S. Rockefeller, David Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller 3rd and Rodman Clark Rockefeller.
The bulk of this collection is Series I, Nelson A. Rockefeller. Its subseries include all photographic formats through which Nelson Rockefeller's impressive art collection is recorded: transparencies, negatives, prints, and slides. This photographic record of the modern art collection amassed by Nelson Rockefeller can be used as a whole to understand the diversity of his interests and enormity of his resources. Additionally, since the works of art are described at an item level, this collection can be used to identify works of a particular artists. Major modern artists are included in this photo-catalogue of Nelson Rockefeller's collection: from Picasso to Toulouse-Lautrec, from Arp to Miro. Therefore, this collection will best serve anyone interested in modern art and the collecting habits of Nelson Rockefeller. Among represented media are painting, sculpture, drawing, and prints. Also, the collection of primitive art gathered by Michael C. Rockefeller in New Guinea and brought to New York for installation at the Museum of Primitive Art is documented in Series I. (This collection was ultimately been deposited in the Metropolitan Museum of Art.) Available too in this series are images of the collection of Mexican Folk Art and images of Kykuit (the Rockefeller family home). Also, there are more tha 1,000 negatives of Nelson Rockefeller's silver and china collection. Art, however, is not the only feature of this entire collection. Also available are images of Rockefeller homes, family portraits, and all manner of museum objects and artifacts. In the subsequent series, the collections of Laurance Rockefeller, David Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, and Rodman Rockefeller are available. Laurance was a collector of model airplanes. He was also the recipient of many awards and commendations that are listed here. David Rockefeller too amassed a rather impressive art collection, which has been described at the item level. Fewer items belonging to John D. Rockefeller 3rd and Rodman Rockefeller are represented in this collection.
Arrangement
The Charles Uht Photograph collection is arranged in 5 Series: Series I - NAR. Series II - LSR. Series III - DR. Series IV - JDR 3rd. Series V - RCR.
Series I contains the most variety in size and format of materials. The subseries headings are consistent throughout the entire collection. However Series I is the only series with slides, 35mm negatives, and printed material.
All five series are organized first by size then by format, following the structure below: 1= 4X5, 2=5X7, 3=8X10, 4=11X14, 5=Slides, 6=35mm, 7=Printed Materials; .1=Transparencies, .2=Negatives, .3=Prints.
All subseries begin with the size of the material, and the second number indicates format. For example, 1.1 indicates 4X5 Transparencies, 2.2 indicates 5X7 Negatives, and 3.3 indicates 8X10 Prints. Series numbers are indicated at the top of every page of the finding aid. All subsequent ones indicate a hierarchy specific to the subseries. For example, in Series I, 1.1.1 is 4X5 transparencies of Art A-Z and 1.1.2 is 4X5 transparencies of Unidentified Art. Then 1.1.3 is 4X5 transparencies of Kykuit Exteriors.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection was deposited with Rockefeller Archive Center in 1998 by Charles Uht.
Photographs; Art, Modern; Art -- Collectors and collecting; Arts; John D. Rockefeller House (Pocantico Hills, N.Y.); Rockefeller family -- Art collections; Art, Primitive; Folk art; Uht, Charles
- Nelson A. Rockefeller (NAR), I
  - 4x5, Transparencies, Miscellaneous, I_1_1
    - Miscellaneous (Box 5)
  - 4x5, Transparencies, Art A-Z, I_1_1_1
    - Boccioni - States of Mind: Those Who Go (Box 1)
    - Boccioni - States of Mind: Those Who Stay (Box 1)
    - Boccioni - States of Mind: The Farewells (Box 1)
    - Bontecou - Untitled (Box 1)
    - Braque - Clarinet (Box 1)
    - Braque - Unidentified (Box 1)
    - Calder - Large Spiny (Box 1)
    - Cezanne - Boy in Red Waistcoat (Box 1)
    - di Chirico - Song of Love (Box 1)
    - Eielson - Red Quipu (Box 1)
    - Ferber - Calligraph KC (Box 1)
    - Glarner - Mural for Dining Room, 812 Fifth Avenue (Box 1)
    - Hartigan - City Life (Box 1)
    - Hartigan - Unidentified (Box 1)
    - Johnson - John D. Rockefeller, Sr. Portrait (Box 1)
    - Klee - Heroic Strokes of the Bow (Box 1)
    - Klee - Fear (Box 1)
    - Lachaise - Couple (Dans la nuit) (Box 1)
    - Lachaise - Torso (Box 1)
    - Lassaw - Galaxy of Andromeda (Box 1)
    - Leger - Woman with a Book (Box 1)
    - Liberman - NAR in Albany (Box 1)
    - Lichtenstein - Unidentified (Box 1)
    - Lipchitz - Song of Vowels (Box 1)
    - Matisse - View of Collioure and the Sea (Box 1)
    - Miro - Seated Woman (Box 1)
    - Modigliani - The Dreamer (Box 1)
    - Murphy - Laura Spelman Rockefeller Portrait (Box 1)
    - Noguchi - Black Sun (Box 1)
    - Picasso - Guitar on Table (Box 1)
    - Picasso - Student with a Pipe (Box 1)
    - Picasso - Interior with a Girl Drawing (Box 1)
    - Picasso - Toros en Vallauris (Box 1)
    - Picasso - Owl (Box 1)
    - Picasso - Houses on the Hill (Box 1)
    - Picasso - Head (watercolor and gouache) (Box 1)
    - Picasso - Head (watercolor and tempera) (Box 1)
    - Picasso - Woman with Mandolin (Box 1)
    - Picasso - Ladies from D'Avignon (tapestry) (Box 1)
    - Picasso - Guitar (Box 1)
    - Rothko - Unidentified (Box 1)
    - Smith, Tony - Wandering Rocks (Box 1)
    - Tabara - Region de los Shiris (Box 1)
    - Tomlin - Number 5 (Box 1)
    - Wright - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Portrait (Box 1)
  - 4x5, Transparencies, Art Unidentified, I_1_1_2
    - Art - Unidentified (Box 1)
  - 4x5, Transparencies, Kykuit Exteriors, I_1_1_3
    - Kykuit Exeriors (Box 1)
  - 4x5, Negatives, Miscellaneous, I_1_2
    - Miscellaneous (Box 5)
  - 4x5, Negatives, Art Unidentified, I_1_2_2
    - Art - Unidentified (Box 2)
  - 4x5, Negatives, Art, A-Z, I_1_2_1
    - Brancusi - Bird in Space (base, mold) (Box 2)
    - Braque - Unidentified (Box 2)
    - Brooks - Jackson (Box 2)
    - Buckman - Podium (Box 2)
    - Chagall - Unidentified (Box 2)
    - Chinni - Natura Extensa (Box 2)
    - de Segonzac, Denoyer - Unidentified (Box 2)
    - Fleischner - Girl on a Swing (Box 2)
    - Ferber - Calligraph KC (Box 2)
    - Glarner - Mural for Dining Room, 812 Fifth Avenue (Box 2)
    - Horwitt - Sky (Box 2)
    - Hurtado - Unidentified (Box 2)
    - Kelly - Green, Red (Box 2)
    - Kolbe - Kneeling Girl (Box 2)
    - Lachaise - Couple (Dans la nuit) (Box 2)
    - Lachaise - Torso (Box 2)
    - Maillol - Night (Box 2)
    - Mariani - Horse (Box 2)
    - Meadmore - Double Up (Box 2)
    - Moore - Knife Edge Two Pieces (Box 2)
    - Moore - Family Group (Box 2)
    - Motherwell - Granada (Box 2)
    - Nash - Unidentified (Box 2)
    - Picasso - The Bathers (Box 2)
    - Rickey - Five Lines in Parallel Planes (Box 2)
    - Rosati - Lippincott II (Box 2)
    - Tajiri - Granny's Knot (Box 2)
  - 4x5, Negatives, Kykuit Interiors, I_1_2_3
    - Kykuit Interiors (Box 2)
  - 4x5, Negatives, Kykuit Exteriors, I_1_2_4
    - Kykuit Exeriors (Box 2)
  - 4x5, Negatives, Primitive Art Collection, I_1_2_5
    - Primitive Art collection - Figures (Box 2)
    - Primitive Art collection - Gallery Views (Box 2)
    - Primitive Art collection - Heads (Box 2)
    - Primitive Art collection - Masks (Box 2)
    - Primitive Art collection - Miscellaneous (Box 2)
    - Primitive Art collection - Shields (Box 2)
    - Primitive Art collection - Stools (Box 2)
    - Primitive Art collection - Textiles (Box 2)
    - Primitive Art collection - Vessels (Box 2)
  - 4x5, Negatives, Mexican Folk Art Collection, I_1_2_6
    - Mexican Folk Art Collection (Box 3)
  - 4x5, Negatives, Mauze Home, I_1_2_7
    - Mauze Home - Interiors (Box 3)
  - 4x5, Negatives, NAR Albany, I_1_2_8
    - NAR - Albany (Box 3)
  - 4x5, Negatives, 1-1043 Silver/China, I_1_2_9
    - 1-1043 Silver/China (Box 3)
    - 1-1043 Silver/China (Box 4)
  - 4x5, Negatives, Rockefeller family, I_1_2_10
    - Rockefeller family (Box 4)
  - 4x5, Prints, Miscellaneous, I_1_3
    - Miscellaneous (Box 5)
  - 4x5, Prints, Kykuit Interiors, I_1_3_1
    - Kykuit Interiors (Box 5)
  - 4x5, Prints, Kykuit Exteriors, I_1_3_2
    - Kykuit Exeriors (Box 5)
  - 5x7, Transparencies, Art, I_2_1
    - Picasso - Girl Before Mirror (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Unknown (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 5x7, Negatives, Interiors, I_2_2
    - Church (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller - Home (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller - Vases (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller - Rugs (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller - Rockefeller family (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 5x7, Prints, I_2_3
    - Glarner Installation, Dining Room, 812 Fifth Avenue (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Primitive Art - Gallery Views (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - NAR with Shirley Temple (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Picasso - Ladies of Avignon (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Picasso - Unknown (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 8x10, Transparencies, Art A-Z, I_3_1_1
    - Boccioni - States of Mind: The Farewells (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Braque - Clarinet (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Braque - The Table (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Braque - Guitar, Newspaper, and Bottle (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Braque - Unidentified (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - di Chirico - Song of Love (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Delvaux - Unidentified (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - van Dongen - Woman in Large Hat (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Glarner - Mural for Dining Room, 812 Fifth Avenue (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Glarner - Tondo 36 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Gorky - Unidentified (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Guston - Unidentified (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Hartigan - City Life (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Henderson - Unidentified (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Jawlensky - The Spanish Girl (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Johns - 0 Through 9 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Kandinsky - Autumn Landscape, Murnau (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Klee - Heroic Strokes of the Bow (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Klee - Yellow Harbor (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Klee - Sharp Profile (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Klee - The Prince (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Leger - Mural for Fireplace, 812 Fifth Avenue (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Lehmbruck - Torso (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Matisse - Mural for Fireplace, 812 Fifth Avenue (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Matisse - Odalisque (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Matisse - Italian Woman (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Miro - Hirondelle/Amour (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Modigliani - The Dreamer (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Moore, Henry - Knife Edge Two Pieces (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Moses - Unidentified (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Nagare - Jubilee (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Picasso - Glasses and Fruits (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Picasso - Guitar on Table (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Picasso - Harlequin (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Picasso - Harvesters (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Picasso - Head (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Picasso - Houses on the Hill (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Picasso - Interior with a Girl Drawing (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Picasso - Kneeling Woman (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Picasso - Pitcher and Bowl of Fruit (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Picasso - Still Life: Le Torero (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Picasso - The Bathers (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Picasso - The Striped Bodice (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Picasso - Unidentified tapestry (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Picasso - Woman with Mandolin (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Rothko - White and Green in Blue (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Rothko - Unidentified (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Sargent - John D. Rockefeller, Sr., Portrait (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Stuart - George Washington, Portrait (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Smith, David - The Banquet (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Unidentified (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - 8x10, Negatives, I_3_2
    - Unidentified Urn (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Primitive Art - Masks (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Rockefeller family Homes - Interiors (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - 8x10, Prints, Art A-Z, I_3_3_1
    - Barnard - The Rising Woman (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Barnard - Adam and Eve (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Bill - Triangular Surface in Space (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Boccioni - States of Mind: The Farewells (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Boccioni - States of Mind: Those Who Go (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Brancusi - Bird in Space (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Braque - Clarinet (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Butler - Girl with a Vest (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Calder - Large Spiny (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Calder - Mobile in Black and Silver (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Calder - The Golfer (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Chagall - Window, Union Church (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Chagall - Drawing for NAR (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Chu Ching - Four Small Birds in Limbs of Tree (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Daumier - Unidentified (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Davidson - John D. Rockefeller, Sr. Bust (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Deruet - Louis XIV King of France (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Fleischner - Girl on a Swing (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Frost - Teeing Off (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Johnson - John D. Rockefeller, Sr. Portrait (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Kingman - Unidentified (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Koenig - Cross IV (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Lachaise - Couple (Dans la nuit) (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Lachaise - Standing Woman (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Lachaise - Standing Control (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Lachaise - Torso (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Lebrun - Unidentified paintings (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Lehmbruck - Torso (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Leger - Mural for Fireplace, 812 Fifth Avenue (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Liberman - NAR in Albany (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Liberman - Unidentified (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Lipchtiz - Song of the Vowels (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Loew - Young Girl Seated on a Tree Stump (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Maillol - Chained Action: Torso of the Monument? (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Maillol - Night (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Maillol - Bather Putting up Her Hair (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Marcks - Maja (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Matisse - Mural for Fireplace, 812 Fifth Avenue (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Matisse - Odalisque (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Matisse - Odalisque in Striped Pantaloons (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Matisse - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Memorial Window, Union Church (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Meadmore - Double Up (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Moore - Knife Edge Two Pieces (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Nadelman - Circus Woman, I (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Nadelman - Circus Woman, II (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Nevelson - Atmosphere and Environment (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Paolozzi - Akapotic Rose (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Pennell - Building the Standard Oil Building (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Redon - Unidentified (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Rickey - Five Lines in Parallel Planes (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Rosati - Lippincott II (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Salisbury - Abby Rockefeller Mauze Portrait (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Salisbury - John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Portrait (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Sargent - John D. Rockefeller, Sr., Portrait (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Smith, David - The Banquet (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Smith, Tony - Wandering Rocks (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Taylor - Gazebo (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Trova - Study: Falling Man (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Picasso - 15 unidentified drawings/paintings/tapestries (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Picasso - Figures and Bulls (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Picasso - Interior with a Girl Drawing (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Picasso - Kneeling Woman (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Picasso - Ladies from D'Avignon (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Picasso - Owl (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Picasso - The Models, III (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Picasso - The Striped Bodice (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Picasso - Woman and Dwarf (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Picasso - Woman with Mandolin (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Unsigned Art - Maiden Holding a Ewer KC493 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Unsigned Art - Standing Figure of Nobleman KC457 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Unsigned Art - Gravestone of Wife of Johannes de Lalata KC452 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Urn KC478 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Girl with Dove KC480 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - St. Michael KC459 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Diane KC479 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Bodhisattva (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Unidentified (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - 8x10, Prints, Primitive Art, I_3_3_2
    - Figures (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Figures (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Figures (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Figures (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Exteriors (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Gallery Views (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Iron Plates (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Masks (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Shields (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Heads (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Jewelry (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Textiles (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Urns, Stools, Drum, Vessels (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Gallery Views (Box 15, Folder 53-56)
  - 8x10, Prints, Coach Prints, I_3_3_3
    - Coach Prints at Kykuit - The Royal Mails Preparing to Start for West of England KC74 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Coach Prints at Kykuit - Light Post Coach KC89 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Coach Prints at Kykuit - Patent Stage Coach KC93 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Coach Prints at Kykuit - The Day Before Christmas the Norwich Coach Going to London KC106 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Coach Prints at Kykuit - Stage KC107 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Coach Prints at Kykuit - Scenes on the Road; Hyde Park Corner KC112 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Coach Prints at Kykuit - Four in Hand KC114 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Coach Prints at Kykuit - Scenes on the Road Kennington Gate KC115 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Coach Prints at Kykuit - The Age: Brighton Coach 1852 KC147 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - 8x10, Prints, Rockefeller Homes and family prints, I_3_3_4
    - Rockefeller family Homes - Interiors (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - Rockefeller family Homes - Exteriors (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - Kykuit - Installing Outdoor Sculpture (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - Rockefeller family (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - Installing Glarner - 812 Fifth Avenue (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - 8x10, Prints, NAR, I_3_3_5
    - NAR (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - NAR - Albany office (Box 17, Folder 64)
    - NAR and Betty Ford (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - 8x10, Prints, Other Art, I_3_3_6
    - Modern Art Exhibit (Box 17, Folder 66)
    - Mexican Folk Art Collection (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - 11x14, Prints, Home Interiors, I_4_3_1
    - Home Interiors (Box 18)
  - 11x14, Prints, Art/Primitive Art, I_4_3_2
    - Bodhisattva (Box 19)
    - Lachaise - Couple (Dans la Nuit) (Box 19)
    - Matisse - Odalisque in Stripped Pantaloons (Box 19)
    - Unidentified (Box 19)
    - Figures (Box 19)
    - Jewelry (Box 19)
    - Iron Plates (Box 19)
  - Slides, Art A-Z, I_5
    - Andrews - Rider (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Armitage - Model for Krefield Monument (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Arp - Homme au Moustache (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Bate - City at Night (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Bontecou - Untitled (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Braque - Composition (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Braque - Helios (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Calder - Flying Boomerangs (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Calder - Model for Large Mobile (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Callery - Letter C Sculpture (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Calo - Sculpture (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Cesar - Scarab (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Cezanne - The Bathers (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Comtois - Reve des Iles, 5 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - de Kooning - Ganesvoort St. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Dehner - Aracnum (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Dufy - La Negresse (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Durchanek - Homo Derelicto (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Frakenthaler - Yellow Clearing (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Fransconi - Monterey Fisherman (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Fransconi - Sardine Fisherman (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Glarner - Relational Painting (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Glarner - Tondo 36 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Gottlieb - Transfiguration (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Greif - Gladiator (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Hart - Miami Beach (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Hartigan - Peonies Hydrangeas (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Hartigan - Salome (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Hayes - Woman Dressing (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Hepworth - Green Globe (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Hinman - Number 3 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Klee - Fear (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Kline - Corinthians II (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Kobashi - Black Composition with Red, Blue, and Yellow (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Kobashi - Composition Arched Lines (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Kobashi - Eclipse (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Kobashi - Plumbobs (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Konzal - 3 pieces, no titles (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Lam - Chemical Nuptials (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Langlais - The Islands (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Lassaw - Galaxy of Andromeda (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Leger - Tapestry after Composition Mono (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Lipton - The Cloak (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Lipton - Storm Bird (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Lyte - Navigo (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Mallary - Icarus (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Mallary - Head of a Bull (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Martins - Bird (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Marini - Portrait of Nelson A. Rockefeller (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Marisol - Exotic Configuration (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Mathieu - Black and White on Brown (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Matisse - Head of a Girl (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Miki - Ear (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Miro - Hirondelle Amour (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Miro - Seated Woman (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Muccini - Tragic Moment (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Nadelman - Two Figures (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Negret - Magic Apparatus (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Noguchi - Mr. One-Man (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Pascan - En Floride (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Pascan - Plage Americaine (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Picasso - Bacchanale II (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Picasso - Coiffure or Woman Combing her Hair (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Picasso - Etude des Profils (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Picasso - Le Depart (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Picasso - Tapestry after La Guernica (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Picasso - Tapestry after Three Musicians (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Picasso - Toros en Vallauris (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Picasso - Two Clowns (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Pignon - Jasmine Pickers (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Reinhoud - Les Helices (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Roberts - Use Fork, NY. Idaho Up. (NAR Campaign Poster) (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Ronald - Spice (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Salles - Hamlet (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Schrag - Meadow on the Island (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Seley - Magister Ludi (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Somaini - Wounded, III (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Stankiewitz - Untitled (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Sugai - Oki (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Toulouse-Lautrec - Adolphe ou les Jeune Homme Triste (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Toulouse-Lautrec - Marcelle Lender (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Toulouse-Lautrec - Miss May Belfort Salutant (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Toulouse-Lautrec - Nuit Blanche (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Toulouse-Lautrec - Yahne et Atoine (Box 20, Folder 15)